Guide to the Sand Hill Road Development Videorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Sand Hill Road development videorecordings
1996-1997
V0173
City of Palo Alto.
4 Linear feet 32 videotapes (VHS)
These video tapes pertain to Stanford University's development plan for the Sand Hill Road corridor between El Camino Real and Santa Cruz Avenue, which falls under the jurisdiction of the City of Palo Alto. Meetings of Palo Alto agencies recorded include Historic Resources Board, July 17, 1996, and Jan. 9, 1997; Architectural Review Board, July, September and October 1996; Planning Commission, July 1996 - January 1997; and City Council meetings, January - May 1997. Other tapes are a special meeting of the Palo Alto and Menlo Park City Councils, December 1996; and computer animations of Sand Hill Road projects, July 1996.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, 1998.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
These videotapes pertain to Stanford University's development plan for the Sand Hill Road corridor between El Camino Real and Santa Cruz Avenue, which falls under the jurisdiction of the City of Palo Alto. Meetings of Palo Alto agencies recorded include Historic Resources Board, July 17, 1996, and Jan. 9, 1997; Architectural Review Board, July, September and October 1996; Planning Commission, July 1996 - January 1997; and City Council meetings, January - May 1997. Other tapes are a special meeting of the Palo Alto and Menlo Park City Councils, December 1996; and computer animations of Sand Hill Road projects, July 1996.
Access Terms
City of Palo Alto.; Palo Alto Planning Commission.; Stanford University -- General subdivision--Planning.;; Land use--Planning--California--Santa Clara County.
Collection Contents
- Videos
  - Historic Resources Board, July 17, 1996, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Architectural Review Board, July 18, 1996, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Palo Alto Planning Commission, July 24, 1996, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Palo Alto Planning Commission, July 31, 1996, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Palo Alto Planning Commission special meeting, Aug. 1, 1996, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Palo Alto Planning Commission special meeting, Aug. 3, 1996, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Palo Alto Planning Commission, Aug. 7, 1996, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Palo Alto Planning Commission, Aug. 28, 1996, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Palo Alto Planning Commission, Sept. 12, 1996, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Palo Alto Planning Commission, Oct. 15, 1996, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Special meeting of Palo Alto and Menlo Park City Councils, Dec. 12, 1996, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Historic Resources Board, Jan. 9, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Palo Alto Planning Commission special meeting, Jan. 11, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Palo Alto City Council, Jan. 27, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Palo Alto City Council, Jan. 30, 1997 (adjourned from Jan. 27), 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Palo Alto City Council, Feb. 4, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Palo Alto City Council, Feb. 6, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Palo Alto City Council, Feb. 8, 1997 (adjourned from Feb. 6), 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Palo Alto City Council, Feb. 11, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Palo Alto City Council, Feb. 26, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Palo Alto City Council, March 3, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Palo Alto City Council, March 5, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Palo Alto City Council, March 11, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Palo Alto City Council, March 12, 1997 (adjourned from March 11), 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Palo Alto City Council, March 17, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Palo Alto City Council, March 18, 1997 (adjourned from March 17, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Palo Alto City Council, March 26, 1997 ((adjourned from March 18), 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Palo Alto City Council, April 8, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Palo Alto City Council, April 29, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Palo Alto City Council, May 27, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Palo Alto City Council, May 28, 1997, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Sand Hill Road Projects Computer Animations, July 1996, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3, Folder 32)